-真的吗  -真的
- They do? - Yeah, they do.
你在哪工作  联邦调查局吗
So you're working for the, uh... What are you, FBI or something?
我儿子说你在联邦调查局
My son says you're in the FBI.
不是的  没那么夸张
No, it's nothing fun like that. That's a little,
还没做到那个级别
a little bit out of my-my pay grade.
我是负责护照的
I'm a passport specialist.
那是做什么的  是...
Oh, okay, what's that? It's, uh...?
-国务院的  -国务院  对的
- State Department. - State Department. Yeah.
你在哪做什么
What the fuck you doing over there?
我读的电信专业
Majored in telecommunications.
有一半墨西哥血统  所以我很乐意
Half Mexican, so I got an invested interest
打击城市里的歧视
in fighting discrimination in the city.
那很不错
That's fantastic.
买点汽水来  还有番茄酱
Hey, go get some soda and, uh, the ketchup.
-所以你是个理想主义者  -是的
- So you're saying you're an idealist. Yeah, man. - Yeah.